- 어서와
- 그래! 좋아, 좋다구!
- Hey.
- Yeah. Yeah, okay. Sure.
어젯밤 일어난 사태에
대해 얘기좀 해볼까?
Look, can we talk
about what happened here last night?
나도 너처럼 아닌 밤중에
홍두깨처럼 말해볼게
Sure. Just give me a second
to get all huffy and weird like you.
어젯밤 누군가 여기서 무슨 일을
저질렀는데 정말 그랬을까? 응?!
You believe that whoever did something
last night did what they did or didn't do?
내가 무슨 말하는지 모르는구나
Okay, you really don't know
what I'm talking about?
- 몰라
- 어제 파티 끝나고
- No.
- Okay. Last night, after the party..
저 발코니에서 레이첼이
회사 남자랑 키스했어!
I saw Rachel kissing that jerk
from her office out on your balcony.
우리 발코니에서? 정말?
Our balcony? Seriously?
발코니에 등을 달자고 했더니
That's so funny. I told Monica
we should put lights on our balcony..
모니카는 추워서
아무도 안나간대, 그래서 난
and she said, "No, no. It's too cold.
Nobody will go out there." And I said:
등을 달면 사람들이
나갈 거라고 했지
"Maybe if we put some lights
out there they will."
그래, 나도 그 얘기를
하러 온거야, 레이첼이
Right, that's what I came over to talk
about. I saw Rachel kissing some guy..
저기서 남자랑 키스를
했다구! 불도 없는데 말야!
on your balcony,
even though there were no lights!
레이첼한테 얘기할거야?
So are you gonna talk to her?
왜? 왜 그래야 하는데?
마음대로 하라고 해! 괜찮아!
Why? Why should I? I mean,
if she wants to move on, that's fine.
"괜찮아"란 말을 진심으로 할땐
목청이 커지고 침까지 튀지
You know when "that's fine" sounds
true? When someone yells it and spits.
정말이야, 남자 만나고 싶음
만나라고해, 난 상관없어
No, I'm serious. I mean, if she wants
to date people, fine. I don't care.
하지만 적어도 나한테
말은 해야지!
But at least she could have told me.
난 내 생활 다 접어놓고
엠마한테 온 힘을 쏟고 있는데
You know, I've been putting my life
on hold and concentrating on Emma.
잘 알지도 못하는 남자랑 키스를 해?
좋아! 나도 똑같이 할거야!
But if she wants to go out there kissing
guys she barely knows, then so will I.
그래, 나 게이다! 하하!
Very funny! Ross is gay!
그래, 너도 네 길을 가
No, no.
Good, so you're moving on.
그런데 갈데는 있어?
Do you have any idea
where you're moving on to?
기회는 아주 많아
I've got plenty of opportunities.
조금전에도 카페에서
여자들이 미소를 보냈다구
Just now, there was some woman
at the coffeehouse smiled at me.
얼마전엔 지하철에서 어떤 여자가
실수로 내 손위에 앉았어
And then the other day on the subway,
a woman "accidentally" sat on my hand.
와, 화려한 싱글 냄새좀
고만 풍겨라!
Dude, don't rub my face
in your crazy single life.
또 한 인류학과 교수는
And there's an anthropologist
at school..
지난번 파티에서
노골적으로 날 꼬셨어
who totally came on to me during
the interdepartmental potluck dinner.
내가 왜 결혼을 했을까!
Why did I get married?
프렌즈 시즌 9
'노래 부르는 모니카'
하나만 물어보자
Hey, let me ask you guys something.
나 내일 새로 사진 찍거든
I'm having new headshots
taken tomorrow.
사진사가 눈썹을 정리하라는데
The photographer said she thinks
I should have my eyebrows waxed.
남자가 좀 웃기지 않을까?
Is that weird for a guy?
- 경우에 따라 다르지
- 무슨 경우?
- Well, it depends.
- On?
그 남자가 성전환 과정의
어디쯤에 있느냐에 따라서
On how far along he is
in the sex-change process.
내 생각은 달라, 남자들이
그러는거 괜찮다고 봐
No, I totally disagree. I think it's fine
for a guy to do something like that.
특히 배우일 경우에는
Especially an actor.
하지만 넌 정리 안해도 돼
네 눈썹은..
I mean, not that you need to.
Your eyebrows are..
알았어, 그만 쳐다봐!
민망하잖아
Stop it, you guys. Stop staring,
you're freaking me out.
넌 손가락에도
털이 많구나!
Your knuckles are kind of hairy too.
그럼 이것도 정리해야 돼?
Oh, man, now I have to get
those done too?
- 와, 돈도 많다!
- 넌 머리 염색하잖아
- Wow, talk about high maintenance.
- You dye your hair.
- 난 여자잖아!
- 이건 성차별이야!
- I'm a woman.
- Double standards!
참, 오늘 마이크의
피아노 바에 올거니?
Before I forget, are you coming
to Mike's piano bar tonight?
나가서 노래부르지
않아도 된다면
- Only if I don't have to get up and sing.
- But everybody sings. It's so fun.
다들 노래하는걸?
굉장히 재미있어
지난번에 어떤 귀여운
아저씨가 무대에 올라갔는데
Last time, this adorable old man got up
there, forgot all the words, flipped out..
가사를 까먹어서 쩔쩔 매고 사람들은
모두 야유해댔어, 엄청 재미있었지
and everyone booed him off the stage.
It was so funny.
난 노래 잘못해
Look, I'm not good at singing.
왜그래? 겁나?
내가 노래 잘부르니까 기가 죽니?
Oh, what's the matter? You scared?
You afraid I'm a better singer?
내가 너 이길까봐 겁나?
You afraid I'm gonna beat you
at singing?
됐어! 그런 수법엔 안넘어가
Nope. Nope. It's not working on me.
와! 나 이제 철들었나봐!
Wow, I must be growing up.
그럼 그냥 마이크 격려만 해줘
노래 안해도 돼
Okay, fine. Just please come and
support Mike. You don't have to sing.
그럼 난 노래 안하고 앉아서
다른 사람 노래 흉봐도 돼?
So I don't have to sing, and I can just sit
there and pass judgment on others?
- 그래, 술도 마시고
- 꼭 갈게
- While drinking.
- I'm there.
안녕, 얘들아
나좀 도와줘
Hi, you guys.
Listen, I really need your help.
바보같은 짓을 저질렀어
I think I did something
really stupid.
그렇긴 하지만 덕분에
이렇게 예쁜 아기가 생겼잖아
Well, yes, Rachel, but you got something
so beautiful out of it.
그거 말구!
어제 개빈하고 키스했어
No, not that.
I kissed Gavin last night.
- 어머!
- 키스를?
- My God.
- You kissed him?
어제 파티 끝나고
발코니에서..
Yeah, it was after the party,
we were on the balcony..
잠깐! 나 집에 있었는데
왜 난 몰랐지?
Wait, wait, wait. I was at home
the whole time. How did I miss that?
파티 끝나고 나서라니까 넌
포장지 다림질하고 있었을 거야
Well, it was the end of the party. You
were probably ironing wrapping paper.
맞다
Oh, yeah.
어쩌다 키스까지 했어?
So how did you end up kissing?
우리 둘뿐이었고
그사람 아주 친절했어
We were all alone
and he was being really nice..
- 그리고 이 스카프도 선물해줬고
- 그남자 싫다며?
- and he gave me this scarf.
- I thought you hated him.
사랑과 미움사이는
종이 한장 차이란다
Well, there is a thin line
between love and hate..
이번 경우엔
스카프 한장이고
and it turns out that line
is a scarf.
그남자랑 잘 해볼 생각이
있는거야?
Are you thinking of starting
something up with this guy?
모르겠어, 너무 복잡해
그사람은 회사 동료고
I don't know. It's so complicated.
I work with this guy.
나한텐 엠마와 로스가 있어
10분 후면 출근해서
I have the baby, and I have Ross.
I don't know what to do.
개빈 얼굴 봐야하는데
어쩌면 좋지?
And I have to be at the office
and see Gavin in 10 minutes.
네가 진심으로 원하는게 뭔지
잘 생각해봐, 개빈하고 얘기해 보고
Sounds like you need to think
about what you want and talk to Gavin.
- 오빠하고도 꼭 얘기해봐
- 그게 아니면..
- And you definitely should talk to Ross.
- Or..
아프다고 결근하면
고민할 필요 없잖아?
I could call in sick
and not deal with it at all.
5개월 출산휴가 후
출근하자마자
Wow! Five months maternity leave,
you're back for four days..
동료와 키스하고
바로 병가를 내?
kiss a co-worker and call in sick.
They are lucky to have you.
능력있는 직원 둬서
너희 회사는 좋겠다!
- 안녕하세요?
- 어서 오세요
- Hi.
- 눈썹 다듬기로 예약했는데요
- 성함이?
- I'm here for my eyebrow appointment.
- Name?
챈들러 빙
Chandler Bing.
네, 잘 오셨어요
Okay, very good.
여기 앉으세요
곧 봐드릴 거예요
Have a seat right here, Mr. Bing,
and Sonya will be right with you.
고마워요
Okay. Thanks.
이걸 만졌어요
I touched the stuff.
제가 닦아드리죠
I'll take care of it.
고마워요
Thanks.
여기 남자들도 많이 오나요?
So do you..?
Do you get a lot of guys in here?
- 그럼요
- 다행이네요
- Oh, absolutely.
- Oh, good.
- 남자손님 소개해드려요?
- 빨리 눈썹이나 해주세요
- You looking to meet somebody?
- All right, let's just do this.
왁스로 정리하기 전에
Okay, we'll get to the wax in a minute.
몇개좀 뽑을게요
First, I want to tweeze
some of the strays, okay?
- 약간 따끔할 거예요
- 난 참을성이 아주 많아요
- Now, this may sting just a little bit.
- I have an extremely high threshold..
엄마야! 맙소사!
내 얼굴! 내 얼굴!
Holy Mother of God!
Oh, my face! My face!
됐어요, 난 괜찮아요
I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm all right.
약간 충격을 받은것 뿐이에요
It's just a bit of shock, that's all.
괜찮으니까 계속하세요
- But I'll be fine. You can go again.
- Okay.
미안해요
Sorry.
아줌마, 미쳤어요?!
아야!
Damn it, woman!
뉴욕 최고의 신랑감이 오셨군
잘되고 있어?
It's the most eligible man in New York.
How's the moving on going?
별로, 지하철에서 이번에도
누가 내 손위에 앉긴 했는데
Not well. I went on the subway again
and someone did sit on my hand..
여자도 아니었고
바지도 안 입었더라구!
but that person was neither female
nor wearing pants.
네가 길을 잘못
선택한 건지도 몰라, 생각해봐
Maybe you're going about this
the wrong way. I mean, think about it:
싱글의 백인남자
이혼경력 세번에 아이가 둘
Single white male, divorced three times,
two illegitimate children.
말이 필요 없잖아
The personal ad writes itself.
그래, 참 재미있다.. 그런데
넌 다시 취직할수 있긴 한거니?
You know, that's funny. Yeah.
So do you think you'll ever work again?
난 있는 그대로
말한것 뿐이야!
What are you doing?
You know I can only dish it out.
다른 남자 만나면서 어떻게
나한테 말을 안할수가 있지?
I can't believe Rachel just moved on
and didn't say anything to me.
별일 아닌지도 몰라
Maybe she didn't move on.
생일 분위기에 충동적으로
한번 그런것일 수도 있다구
Maybe that kiss was just an impulsive,
one-time birthday thing.
한달쯤 전에 술집에서 만난
남자한테 전화번호 준적도 있어
No, a month ago, she gave her number
to some guy in a bar.
- 그남자랑 데이트했어?
- 그남자 전화 내가 받았는데
- Did she go out with him?
- No. When he called..
메시지 안전해줬어
I threw the message away.
암, 당연히 그래야지
The high road.
좋아, 더 얘기할것 없어
나도 여자 만날거야!
All right, you know what? Enough.
Enough talking. I have to get moving.
저기 두 금발여자 어때?
같이가자
Hey, check out those two blonds
over there. Hey, come with me.
나까지 이혼시킬 셈이야?
Are you trying to get
everybody divorced?
넌 아무것도 안해도 돼
둘이 하면 훨씬 쉬울거야
You don't have to do anything.
It'll just be easier if it's two of us.
대학 때처럼 기억나? 네가 먼저
유머로 어색함을 깨는거야
Like college, remember? First, you
break the ice with some kind of a joke..
그럼 내가 끼여들어서
흥미로운 화제를 꺼내는 거지
so they know you're the funny one. I
swoop in with interesting conversation..
그러면 난 똑똑하고 생각이
깊으며 섹시한 남자가 되는 거야
so they'll see that I'm the brilliant,
brooding, sexy one.
네가 나보다 더 웃긴다!
I thought I got to make the jokes.
- 너 취직 안하냐?
- 알았어!
- Don't you have to be at work?
- Oh, come on.
안녕하세요? 난 챈들러예요
여긴 내 친구 로스구요
Hello. Hi, my name's Chandler.
This is my friend Ross right here.
두분이 도와주면
We were wondering..
인간피라미드 만드는데
여섯명만 더 있으면 돼요
if you're up for it, we only need
six more people for a human pyramid.
끼여들어! 끼여들어!
Swoop. Swoop.
어, 신문 읽고 있군요
Hey, I notice
you're reading the paper.
유럽에 또 홍수가 났다죠?
Another flood in Europe, huh?
질문 하나 할게요
Here's a question:
물에 빠져 죽고 싶어요?
불에 타 죽고 싶어요?
Would you rather drown
or be burned alive?
- 미안하지만 가야겠어요
- 네
- I'm sorry, we're just leaving.
- Okay.
우리 실력 여전하네
We still got it.
- 누구세요?
- 개빈이에요, 수프좀 가져왔어요
- Who is it?
- Gavin. I brought you some soup.
- 왜요?
- 아프다고 해서요
- Why?
- I heard you were sick.
맞아요! 잠깐만요
지저분한것 좀 치우구요!
Oh, right! Hold on,
let me just clean up in here a little bit.
안녕하세요?
Hello, Gavin.
오늘 안나와서 걱정했어요
몸은 어때요?
I missed you at work.
How you feeling?
솔직하게 말하죠
많이 아파요
I'm not gonna lie to you, I'm pretty sick.
다행이네요
날 피하려고 결근한게
Oh, good. Because I was having
a totally paranoid moment..
아닌가 걱정했거든요
where I thought you
called in sick to avoid me.
아뇨, 아녜요
Oh, no, no, no.
어제 즐거웠어요
So I had fun last night.
나두요
So did I.
전염되는 거예요?
Exactly how contagious
is this thing you have?
발코니에 나와 있다가
걸린 단순한 감기예요?
Is it a cold from standing on
the balcony, or did a monkey bite you?
아니면 원숭이한테 물렸어요?
- 그냥 감기예요
- 열도 나요?
- It's just a cold.
- Do you have a fever?
어디 봅시다
Let me see.
왜요? 왜그래요?
What? What is it?
What's the matter?
저사진 속에서 로스가
뭘하고 있는거죠?
What's Ross doing to you
in that picture?
화석발굴용 붓으로
나한테서 먼지를 터는 거예요
Oh, he's dusting me with a fossil brush.
저러면 재미있을 거라면서
He thought it would be funny.
- 그랬군요
- 네
- Right. Right.
- Yeah.
- 로스
- 네
- Ross.
- Yeah.
두사람은 어떤 관계죠?
난 중간에 끼여들고 싶은 생각 없어요
What's the deal with you guys? I don't
wanna get in the middle of anything.
아뇨, 아무 관계 아녜요
로스는 신경쓰지 말아요
You're not getting in the middle
of anything. Don't worry about Ross.
숨어요! 로스예요!
Hide! That's Ross! Hide!
- 어서 숨어요!
- 신경쓰지 말라면서요?
- Hide! Hide!
- Yeah, but you said not to worry..
거짓말이에요! 아픈것도 꾀병이고!
빨리 숨기나 해요!
I lied and I'm not sick either!
Just stay behind the curtain!
- 안녕?
- 오, 몰리, 로스인줄 알았어요
- Hi.
- Oh, Molly. You're not Ross.
엠마를 어머님께 데려다 주러
왔어요, 기억하죠?
No. I'm here to take Emma
to your mother's, remember?
맞아요, 그랬죠
Right. Yes, yes.
- 놀라지 말아요
- 왜요?
- Don't panic.
- What?
커튼 뒤에 남자가 있어요!
There is a man behind your curtain.
- 나한테 가스총이 있어요
- 아뇨! 괜찮아요! 그런거 아녜요
- I have Mace in my purse.
- No, that's okay! No, no, no.
회사동료 개빈 인데
실없는 장난을 치고 있죠
This is my business associate Gavin
being silly. Come out from behind there.
커튼 뒤에서 나와요, 개빈!
개빈입니다
반가워요
Hi. Gavin. Pleased to meet you.
제가 저기 숨겠다고 했어요
It was my idea to stand there.
네, 반가워요
엠마 데리고 나올게요
- Hello. I'll just go get Emma.
- Okay.
왜..
So..
- 숨으라고 했죠?
- 로스인줄 알았으니까요
- why did I have to hide?
- I thought it was Ross.
그래서요? 두사람 특별한
사이 아니라면서요
I thought there was nothing
going on between you.
맞아요
특별한 사이 아녜요
There isn't. There totally isn't.
문소리 나니까 꼭 난생처음 로데오
경기 나온 망아지처럼 뛰더군요
You hear keys in the hall and you jump
like a bronco coming out of the chute.
전에 로데오 경기
바람잡이였어요
I used to be a rodeo clown.
있잖아요, 개빈
All right, look, Gavin..
개빈이 여기 있다는게
왠지 찔려요
I guess I felt guilty
that you were here..
그럴 필요 없는데..
which I shouldn't.
로스와 지금 사귀고
있지는 않지만
You know, Ross and l
are not in a relationship..
로스는 엠마의 아빠예요
그리고 알다시피
but he is the father of my child.
And, you know..
같이살죠, 게다가
우리 둘 역사가 꽤 길어요
we do live together. And plus,
there's just so much history, you know?
나도 모르겠어요
It's just..
I don't know.
- 미안해요, 모든게 너무 복잡해요
- 괜찮아요
- I'm sorry. I'm just all over the place.
- It's okay.
내가 있을 자리가 아니군요
충고 한마디 해도 되겠어요?
It's probably not my place,
but can I give you a piece of advice?
- 네
- 로스와 진지하게 얘기해봐요
- Yes.
- You should talk to Ross about all this.
다들 그렇게 얘기하더군요
People keep saying that.
미안해요, 개빈
I'm sorry, Gavin.
미안할것 없어요
Don't be.
시기가 나빴을 뿐이죠
It's just bad timing.
그런데 정말
로데오 바람잡이였어요?
So seriously, rodeo clown?
그럼요! 최고였죠!
One of the best, ma'am.
One of the best.
'피아노 바 & 카바레'
패배자에게 기회는 없어
왜냐하면 우린
이세상의 승리자니까
아, 여자 친구예요
누구한테나 이러는게 아닙니다
Oh, she's my girlfriend.
That's not just how we do it here.
잠깐 쉬겠습니다
잠시후
I'm gonna take a little break,
and when we come back..
케네스 차례예요
곡목은 "내몸을 어루만지네"
we've got Kenneth singing
"I Touch Myself."
전 심사위원이 아닙니다
I'm not here to judge.
- 너도 노래해
- 못한다고 했잖아
- You have got to sing.
- No, I told you I can't.
정말 재미있을 거야
너 목소리도 좋잖아
But you would have so much fun.
And you have a really nice voice.
- 내 노래를 언제 들었는데?
- 너 요리할 때마다 듣지
- When have you heard me sing?
- All the time, when you're cooking.
- 뭐?
- 늘 노래부르잖아
- What?
- Yeah, you're always singing:
냠냠냠
내 뱃속엔 사랑이 가득
Yummy, yummy, yummy
I've got love in my tummy
그노래는 좀 하지
Yeah, I do rock that one.
무대에 올라가고 싶은 마음
정말 조금도 없는거야?
Isn't there just a little part of you
that wants to get up there?
글쎄, 조금은..
아냐, 너무 겁나!
Just a little. But, God, it's so scary.
뭘 불러야 할지도 모르겠고
I don't even know what I would sing.
- 노래책 갖다줄게요
- "델타 던" 부를게요!
- Well, I've got a book around..
- "Delta Dawn."
안녕, 눈을 뗄수가 없더군요
목걸이가 아주 독특한데요?
Hi. I couldn't help but notice,
but that's an unusual necklace.
한시간 전에도
나한테 집적였잖아요?
You already hit on me an hour ago.
확실한 거절의 뜻이군요?
Right. So that's a firm no?
이해가 안돼!
번번이 퇴짜야!
I don't believe this.
I just keep striking out.
나도 정말 이해가 안된다!
I don't get it either.
너처럼 구차하게 매달리고
I mean, you're obviously desperate.
어떻게 죽고 싶냐고 물어보는
남자를 퇴짜놓다니!
You're asking women
how they wanna be killed.
레이첼은 여러 남자 만나 뽀뽀하며
This is great.
Rachel's gonna keep kissing guys..
맘에 드는 남자 찾을 텐데
난 혼자 외롭게 죽겠지
until she finds the one she wants,
and I'm gonna die alone.
물에 빠져서? 아니면..?
By drowning or..?
- 대체 내가 왜 싫대?
- 나도 모르겠다
- Why would he break up with me?
- I don't know, sweetie.
난 그이를 사랑했고 그이한테서
사랑 받고 싶었을 뿐이야!
All I ever wanted was to just love him
and have him love me back.
내가 그렇게 매력이 없니?
I mean, am I so unlovable?
- 에구!
- 딱이야!
- Wow.
- I know.
고맙습니다, 케네스가
All right. That was Kenneth with his..
"내 몸을 어루만지네"를
온몸으로 표현해줬네요
much too literal rendition
of "I Touch Myself."
다음은 모니카!
곡목은 "델타 던"!
Coming up next, we've got Monica
singing "Delta Dawn."
어떡해! 사람들 앞에서
어떻게 노래를 불러!
Wait. I can't sing in
front of all these people.
사람들 없다고 생각해
Just pretend they're not
even here. It's okay.
조명이 비추면 너무 밝아서
아무것도 안보여, 어서가
Once that spotlight hits you, it's so bright,
you won't see anyone anyway.
모니카예요
"델타 던" 부를게요
Hi, I'm Monica. And I'm going
to be singing "Delta Dawn."
델타 던, 그꽃은 무엇인지
지나간 시절의 시든 장미일까
- 마이크도 모니카 속살 보여요?
- X-레이처럼
- Can you totally see through her shirt?
- Like an x-ray.
하필 이런 날
브래지어를 안하다니
Bad day not to wear a bra.
날 하늘의 저택으로
데려가 줘요
41살인 그녀를
아버지는 아가라 부르시네
광고직 사원을 구한다고
해서 전화 드려요
I'm calling about the advertising job.
네, 말단 사원을
채용하신다고 들었어요
Yes, I realize it would be entry level.
그럼, 치킨 인형을
입어야 하나요?
Oh, so would I actually
have to wear the chicken suit?
야, 나좀 도와줘
I need your help.
심각한 일인가 본데?
Wow, it seems serious.
무슨 문제죠, 애쉴리 저드?
What seems to be the problem,
Ashley Judd?
나 사진 새로 찍어야 하거든
그래서 눈썹을 정리했어
I'm getting new headshots taken.
So I went to get my eyebrows shaped.
잠깐! 나 지금 농담
한마디만 하면 안돼?
I'm sorry.
Moment to make fun of that, please.
여자같은 짓을 하긴 했지만
너쯤은 때려눕힐수 있어!
I may be a sissy, but I'll still
pound you into the ground.
너무 아파서 한쪽 눈썹만
하고 와버렸어, 그랬더니..
Look, it hurt so bad, I could only
let her do one eyebrow, and now..
짝짝이가 됐어!
they don't match!
꼭 아기 애벌레가 엄마 애벌레
쫓아가는것 같다!
It's like a baby caterpillar
chasing its mama.
나좀 도와줘!
매직펜 가져왔어
You got to help me out, okay?
Look, I have a magic marker.
얇은 눈썹좀 덧칠해봐
사진에 이상하게 나오지 않게
Fill in the skinny one
so I don't look stupid for my pictures.
이거 초록색 펜인데?
Okay, first of all, this is green.
- 젠장! 그럼 나 어떡해!
- 도와줄테니까
- What the hell am I supposed to do?!
- I will help you out..
너도 약속 한가지해
지금 하는말 아무한테도 안한다고
but you have to promise you won't
tell anyone what I'm about to tell you.
뭔데?
What? What?
그러니까
Okay.
애들은 보통 잔디를 깎거나
You know how most kids get their
allowance from mowing the lawn..
쓰레기를 버리고 용돈 받지?
or taking out the garbage?
Well, I earned mine..
난 아빠 눈썹 정리하고 용돈 받았어
아빠 파트너 눈썹도
by plucking the eyebrows of my father
and his "business partners."
맙소사!
Oh, my God.
내 도움이 필요 없나보지?
아수라 백작?
Yeah, well, I guess you don't need
my help, Victor-Victoria.
아냐, 필요해!
진짜진짜 필요해
No, no, no. I do. I do.
I need your help.
그런데 눈썹은 더 못뽑겠어
아파 죽는줄 알았다구!
But, Chandler, I don't know if I can take
any more plucking. It hurt so bad.
얼음과 알로에
자기혐오로 가득찬
Not with my combination of ice cubes,
aloe vera and my gentle..
내 부드러운 손길이면
문제없어
self-loathing touch.
날 하늘의 저택으로
데려가 줘요
미안해요
노래 끝났어요!
I'm sorry, the song's over.
- 나봤어?
- 아주 속속들이 봤지
- Did you see me up there?
- Every little bit of you.
사람들 앞에서 노래하고
사람들이 날 좋아하다니 굉장해!
I can't believe I sang
in front of people and they liked me.
어떤 사람은 "저 팁좀 봐!"
라고 소리치던걸!
Did you hear that guy shouting,
"Look at those tips"?
정말 내 덕분에
팁이 많이 들어왔어요?
I mean, did I really help
you get a lot of tips?
그럼요
Sure.
모니카, 네 노래가
- Mon, not that you didn't sound good..
- Good?
- 나빴다는건 아닌데..
- 무슨 소리야?
사람들 환호소리 못들었어?
나 굉장했다구!
Didn't you hear them? I was great!
이런 기회줘서 정말 고마워
너무 값진 선물이야!
Thank you so much for making me
do this. That is the best gift ever.
속옷도 아주
좋은 선물이죠
Also a good gift: underwear.
정말 고마워요
Thank you so much
for letting me do this.
공중화장실은 꺼림칙해서
오줌을 쌀수가 없다니까요
Public bathrooms freak me out. I can't
even pee, let alone do anything else.
그런말을 거리낌없이
할수있는 자세가 중요하죠
But what's great is
you don't mind talking about it.
에릭과 헤어진 날
당신을 만나다니 근사해요!
It is so amazing that I met you on the
same day that Eric broke up with me..
애인을 잃으니까
새 애인이 생기네요!
because it's like, you lose a boyfriend,
and you get a boyfriend.
에릭에 대한 반발심으로
이러는거 절대 아녜요
No, don't worry. This is not some
rebound thing. I am totally over Eric.
에릭은 완전히 잊었어요
탁월한 선택이야, 로스
Good choice, Ross.
집에 있었네!
Hey. Hi. There you are.
- 찾으러 다녔거든
- 그래? 나 여기 있어
- I've been looking for you everywhere.
- Hello. Well, here I am.
엄마가 9시까지는
엠마 봐주신대
My mom is not bringing
the baby back until 9:00.
그래서 우리 얘기좀
했으면 좋겠어
So I was hoping you and I
could have a chance to kind of..
- 누구 왔어?
- 그래, 미셸이야
- Somebody here?
- Oh, yeah. That's Michelle.
- 누구?
- 요즘 만나는 여자
- Who?
- Oh, just this woman I've been seeing.
- 만나는 사람 있어?
- 말 안했던가?
- You've been seeing someone?
- Yeah, didn't I mention that?
오래되진 않았지만
I mean, we haven't been
going out too long..
아주 통하는게 많아
but there's this amazing
connection between us.
방금전에도 날
애인이라고 불렀는걸
I mean, in fact just before you came in,
she called me her boyfriend.
좀 빠른것 같지만
느낌이 좋아
I thought it was a little too soon,
but also, it felt kind of nice.
항생제는 왜 먹어요?
What are you taking amoxicillin for?
벌써 내물건 뒤져 볼만큼
How great is this?
You're already comfortable enough..
편한사이가 됐다니 좋네요
to look through my stuff.
미셸, 내 룸메이트 레이첼이에요
I'm sorry, Michelle,
this is my roommate, Rachel.
엠마의 엄마기도 하죠
And I'm also Emma's mother.
- 엠마가 누군데요?
- 딸이 있다고 말했죠?
- Who's Emma?
- I told you about my daughter.
이 아가씨가 딸이에요?
This is your daughter?
내가 아가씨 새 엄마가
될수도 있어!
I could be your new mommy.
다 됐어
And done.
이럴수가!
Oh, my God.
아무 느낌도 없었어!
너 아직 취직 안됐지?
I didn't feel a thing.
Hey, are you still looking for a job?
그 마녀같은 미용사가
일하는 구역 접수해라
Because you could tweeze circles
around that sadistic bitch at the salon.
- 고마워, 어떤지 볼래?
- 그래
- Thanks. Wanna see what it looks like?
- Yeah.
와! 양쪽이 똑같네!
멋있는데?
They totally match.
They look great.
근사해!
반가워요!
They look great. How you doing?
괜찮은것 같다
실은 좀 걱정했었어
Yeah, I think it looks pretty good.
I was a little worried I was..
속에 있던 점이 드러나서 말야
uncovering a birthmark
right about there..
그런데 알고 보니 초콜릿이더라
but it turned out to be
a little piece of chocolate.
- 그래? 챈들러, 정말 고맙다!
- 천만에
- Chandler, thank you so much.
- No problem.
우리가 지금좀
여성스러운 시간을 보냈잖아
Listen, that was a pretty
girlie hour we just spent.
그러니까 이젠좀
남자다운 시간을 갖자
We should do something manly
to make up for it.
그래
Yeah.
- 속눈썹 좀 올려줄래?
- 좋아!
- Curl my eyelashes.
- Yeah!
다음번에는 좀 빠른 곡을
부를까봐
For my next song, I think I'll sing
something a little more upbeat, all right?
포인터 시스터스의
"너무 흥분돼!" 어때?
How about the Pointer Sisters'
"I'm So Excited"?
통통 튀게 반주해줘요
And make it bouncy.
네 실력만으로도
충분 할거야
Well, you can probably take care of that
on your end.
늦어서 미안해
조이를 보면 왜 늦었는지 알거야
I'm sorry I'm late. You'll understand
when you see Joey.
마침 잘왔어
나 노래하려던 참이야
Honey, you're just in time.
I'm about to sing another song.
- 정말? 이 많은 사람들 앞에서?
- 다들 날 좋아해!
- Really? In front of all these people?
- And they love me.
굉장한데!
- Oh, my God.
- She gives the people what they want.
사람들이 보고 싶어하는 걸
보여주거든
앉아서 구경해
All right, watch.
오늘밤 우리
사랑을 나눠요
다른 일은 모두 제쳐두고
때가 되면
사랑을 보여줘요
저거 우리 마누라
젖가슴 맞니?
Are those my wife's nipples?
이상하다! 아까는 안보였는데!
다시는 못 올라가게 해야지
Isn't that funny? I didn't see that before.
I wouldn't have let her go up again.
그만두게 해야겠어!
I've gotta stop this.
내몸으로 당신을 감싸고..
뭐어때!
어쨌든 날 좋아하잖아!
Who cares? They still love me.
너무 흥분돼!
숨길수가 없어..
You, touching yourself! Out!
거기 손장난하는 사람!
나가!
와! 화장실 참 자주 간다
Wow! She does that a lot.
로스? 박사라는 말 안했잖아요
Ross, you didn't tell me
you were a doctor.
뭐? 아직 박사란 말도 안했어?
Wait a minute. You haven't even
told her you are a doctor yet?
만난지 얼마나 된거야?
한시간?
How long have you known her,
like an hour?
한시간 반쯤 됐어요
Actually, about an hour and a half.
만난지 얼마 안됐다고 했잖아
그래도 통하는게 많아
I told you it wasn't long, but there's
an amazing connection between us.
로스도 그렇게 생각해요?
You feel that too?
- 나만 그런줄 알았는데!
- 정말이에요!
- I thought that that was just me.
- Are you kidding?
- 이번 주말에 여행갈래요?
- 생각해보죠
- Do you wanna go away this weekend?
- We'll see.
뭐하는 거야?
Ross, what's going on here?
집에 낯선 여자
막 데려와도 되는거야?
Are we just bringing strange women
back to the apartment now?
글쎄, 발코니에서 남자랑
키스하는건 괜찮나?
I don't know. Are we just kissing
guys on balconies?
- 어떻게 알았어?
- 난 천리안이거든!
- How do you know about that?
- Through the magic of sight.
난 여기서 우리 아기
재우고 있었어
- I was here, putting our child to sleep..
- Emma.
엠마
창밖을 보니까
네가 그 남자랑 키스하더군!
When I looked through the window
and saw you kissing a guy..
안지 1주일이나 됐어?
you've known for what, a week?
그래서 이러는 거야? 그래서
보란듯이 여자를 데려왔어?
God, is that what this is all about?
You bring her up here to get back at me?
제가 기생충 때문에
공중화장실을 못써서
No, actually, see, I had to pee
because I can't use public bathrooms..
- 일보려고 올라왔어요
- 미셸, 그만 가봐요
- because of the doody parasites.
- Okay, Michelle, it's time to go.
- 전화해요
- 그러죠
- Well, call me.
- Okay.
내 전화번호 모르잖아요
Wait, you don't have
my phone number.
우리가 만날 운명이라면
내가 맞출수 있을 거예요
You know what?
If it's meant to be, I'll guess it.
잘가요
Bye-bye.
대단해!
Score.
왜, 마음에 안들어?
자기의 발코니 키스파티에
Did you not like her? Because I was
hoping we could come..
우리도 참석할까 했는데?
to your kissing parties
on the balcony.
이렇게 과민 반응하는 게
난 도무지 이해가 안가! 단 한번
I can't believe you are making a big deal
about this. It was one kiss!
- 한사람과 키스한것 뿐이야!
- 아, 그래?
- One guy. One time!
- Oh, really?
- 그래
- 그러셔?
- Yeah.
- Oh, really?
그래!
Oh, yeah.
- 그럼 술집에서 만난 남자는 뭐지?
- 누구?
- What about the guy from the bar?
- Who?
술집에서 만난 남자한테
전화번호 줬잖아
The guy you gave your number to.
- 그건 또 어떻게 알아?
- 너 찾는 전화 왔었어
- How do you know about that?
- Because he called here looking for you.
그러니까 그 남자랑 키스한게
일회성이라고 말하지마
So don't tell me kissing this guy
from work is a one-time thing.
한달동안 술집에서 남자 만나고
Because you've been out there
in bars and on balconies..
발코니에서 남자랑 키스했으면서
나한테 단 한마디도 하지 않았어!
for over a month now. And you
don't even have the courtesy to tell me.
- 내가 왜 몰랐지?
- 뭐?
- Why didn't I get that message?
- What?
술집에서 만난 남자 전화
내가 왜 메시지를 못 받았지?
From the guy in the bar?
Why didn't I get that message?
내가 잘 접어서
내 주머니에 넣었거든
Because I folded it up
and put it in my pants pocket.
거기 안 찾아봤어?
Do you not look there?
로스?
Ross.
내가 숨겼어
I never gave it to you.
왜?
Why?
- 나도 몰라
- 도대체..
- I don't know.
- Oh, God, you know what? I don't..
자기가 뭐라고 생각하는거야?
자기가 뭔데
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to decide..
남의 전화메시지를
마음대로 숨겨?
what messages
I should or should not get?!
내가 누구냐구? 난 네가
남자들과 시시덕거릴 동안
Who am I? I'm the guy
who's taking care of our baby..
- 우리 아기를 보살피는 사람이야!
- 기막혀!
- while you're at bars meeting guys!
- I cannot believe you.
난 우리둘에 대해 같이
성숙한 대화를 하고 싶었는데
I actually came in here hoping to have
a mature conversation with you about us.
남의 전화나 가로채고
But I can't do that with someone
who hides my messages..
미친 여자 끌어들이는
사람하곤 말못하겠어!
and brings crazy women
back to my apartment!
멀쩡한 여자들은
안 넘어오더라구!
Hey, none of the sane ones
wanted to come back with me!
어쨌든 요점은 그게 아냐!
요점은..
That's not the point, okay?
The point is..
네가 일언반구 없이
남자를 만나러 다녔다는 거야
you are the one who moved on
and didn't tell anyone.
모든게 엉망이야!
Oh, God, Ross,
this is just so messed up.
우리 뭐가 잘못된 거지? 사람들은
우리를 보고 이상하다고 생각해
What is wrong with us? When people
hear about our situation, they ask:
동거는 하되 연인은 아니면서
애는 낳아 키우니 말야
"You live together, but you're not
a couple, yet you have a baby?
하지만 난 우리만 문제
없다면 괜찮다고 생각했어
Isn't that weird?" And I say,
"No. It's not, because it works for us."
하지만 괜찮지가 않아!
But you know what?
This doesn't work.
- 아니, 문제가 아주 많아!
- 동감이야!
- In fact, this is the opposite of working.
- Clearly.
서로 뜻이
And you know..
맞는다는 조건으로
같이 살기로 한건데
we said that we would live together
as long as this makes sense..
이러면 뜻이 맞는다고
할수가 없어
and maybe this
just doesn't make sense anymore.
그럴지도 몰라
Yeah, maybe not.
그럼 어떻게 하고 싶어?
So, what do you wanna do?
안녕
Hi.
엠마랑 나 여기서 좀 살아도 돼?
Can Emma and I live here for a while?
오, 저런!
God.
물론이지!
- Of course.
- Thank you.
네 눈썹 너무 웃겨!
Your eyebrows look weird.
황소개구리 제레미야는
내 소중한 친구였지
그의 말 이해는 못했지만
술 마시는걸 도와줬어
댁은 아무때나
손장난을 하는군요?
So you'll just touch yourself
for anything, then?